But the point I want to make
here is there's an amazing
lady called, she's called Arlie Russell
Hochschild. And I'm
never comfortable about
that last name when I'm pronouncing
it right. But she has this
concept called emotional labour.
And the point that she makes
is that an awful lot of
the jobs that people do in life, the
work involved is in having
one emotion and then
pretending that you have another emotion.
So for example, air crew, people
who sell soft drinks and duty-free on the
planes, they have to
be pleasant and polite,
even if people are being obnoxious.
Lots of professions,
so nurses and doctors,
they have to be friendly and cheerful,
even if the news is terrible.
Lawyers have to not laugh when their
clients do incredibly stupid things.
So there's this work that
has to be done between the
emotions that you feel and the
emotions that you demonstrate.